Honey...
I decided to take over the Glee Club.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.MY-SUBS.com
My name is Kurt Hummel.
I'm a sophomore at McKinley.
My first day at this school,
Out of the way, fag!
What a joke.
Sorry.
Hope I didn't make you late for remedial math.
What was that?
Nothing. I just...
I just said I was sorry.
Nice.
Hey, bro, don't be gay.
Another day, another cataclysmic humiliation.
Everywhere I go,
I'm isolated and alone.
I know my mom used to tell me how good it made her feel
I don't even remember
I feel like I could die tomorrow
I'm not sure anyone would even notice.
Can I help you?
Oh! No. I'm-I'm sorry.
I-I just made a wrong turn.
What's your name?
Kurt Hummel.
Hi, Kurt. I'm Miss Pillsbury, the guidance counselor.
Are you new to the school?
I'm a sophomore.
That's awkward.
Well, if you ever need anything,
One, two, three, four, five.
Because feelings don't take vacations, do they?
They work in 24-hour shifts.
I mean, I don't.
I'm only here during regular school hours.
And I take vacation.
I try not to eat into my sick days...
It was nice meeting you.
Yeah, it was nice meeting you.
Mm-hmm.
What is that on your hands and your coveralls?
What would you call that?
Is that oil? Is that grease?
Down at the shop, we just call it grime.
Grime.
Look, I know why
Oh, you do? Oh. Oh, dear.
Is Kurt acting strangely at home?
Yeah, since he was two.
Look, I know he's a little bit different,
I mean, kids,
When I was his age,
I was a Bengals fan.
Now I'm a Browns fan,
No, sorry,
I don't think we're talking about the same thing.
Um, I'm worried that Kurt is, uh...
Oh.
No, deeply.
And I'm concerned about him.
Look, I-I walked in on him, and he was reading this.
Hey.
What's up?
Nothing.
Is it time for me to start dinner?
Uh, in a minute.
I, uh...
I got called into school by your guidance counselor today.
She told me... some upsetting stuff.
I'm fine, Dad.
She's... she's just overreacting.
Look, Kurt, I don't want to talk
You do your thing, I do mine.
But you're all alone down here, most of the time.
You don't have any friends.
You don't understand.
School is very complicated for me.
I was a teenager;
I get the pressure.
Making friends... that's why
I joined the football team.
You want me to join the football team?
Look, I'm not asking here, Kurt.
This is an order.
By the end of this week,
I want you on a team,
May I sit here?
Be careful with the posters.
They take 20 minutes each to make.
Okay.
I see you're in the Speech Club.
Speech Club, Renaissance Club,
Black Student Union.
It's important for me to be immersed in all cultures.
I'm an actress.
Oh, I know. I've seen your videos on MySpace.
You're very talented.
I'm Rachel Berry.
Kurt Hummel.
Well, perhaps I should join the Speech Club.
My-my dad's making me join something.
And to be honest with you,
I have also been
I'm not toying around with anything.
The minute I graduate, I'm going directly to Broadway
Besides, you can't join the Speech Club; it's full.
- Oh.
- Can you carry a tune?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
- Because I don't know
Mr. Ryerson, was in charge,
He's the really cool Spanish teacher
Justin Timberlake.
When he was in this school and he was in the Glee Club,
Do you know how hard that is?
I'm assuming that you're a contralto or a mezzo-soprano.
We'll explore your vocal range tomorrow after school.
I'll reserve the auditorium.
♪ Whenever I see someone ♪
♪ Less fortunate than I ♪
♪ And let's face it, who isn't ♪
♪ Less fortunate than I? ♪
♪ My tender heart tends to start to bleed ♪
♪ And when someone needs a makeover ♪
♪ I simply have to take over ♪
♪ I know, I know ♪
♪ Exactly what they need ♪
♪ And even in your case ♪
♪ Though it's the toughest case ♪
♪ I've yet to face ♪
♪ Don't worry ♪
♪ I'm determined to succeed ♪
♪ Follow my lead ♪
♪ And yes, indeed ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Will ♪
♪ Be ♪
♪ Popular ♪
♪ You're gonna be popular ♪
♪ I'll teach you the proper poise ♪
♪ When you talk to boys ♪
♪ Little ways to flirt and flounce ♪
Ooh! ♪ I'll show you what shoes to wear ♪
♪ How to fix your hair ♪
♪ Everything that really counts ♪
♪ To be popular ♪
♪ I'll help you be popular ♪
♪ You'll hang with the right cohorts ♪
♪ You'll be good at sports ♪
♪ Know the slang you've got to know ♪
♪ So let's start
'cause you've got an awfully ♪
♪ Long way to go ♪
♪ Don't be offended by my frank analysis ♪
♪ Think of it as personality dialysis ♪
♪ Now that I've chosen to become a pal ♪
♪ A sister and advisor ♪
♪ There's nobody wiser ♪
♪ Not when it comes to ♪
♪ Popular ♪
♪ I know about popular ♪
♪ And with an assist from me to be who you'll be ♪
♪ Instead of dreary who you were ♪
♪ Well, are ♪
♪ There's nothing that can stop you ♪
♪ From becoming popular ♪
♪ Lar ♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ You'll be popular ♪
♪ Just not quite as popular ♪
♪ As me. ♪
That was incredible!
That is definitely the song that we need to sing
Together?
I'm sorry, Kurt,
When you look at the sky at night, what do you see?
Um... stars?
Exactly.
Some shine brighter than others,
I enjoyed singing with you today
Eat or be eaten.
This is show choir.
Oh! Um, hi.
- Uh, Miss Jones?
- That's me.
I-I'm Kurt Hummel.
Mm-hmm. Kurt Hummel.
And what do you want?
We're walking, we're talking.
Well, I heard that you were a-a total star
Well, that's how you get the big man upstairs' attention.
Well, I want to be just like you.
Kurt, you are... you're adorable.
But I just don't think that this pale, sexy,
Keebler Elf look really fits in with my church choir.
I mean, no offense.
Oh, no, no.
None taken.
No, no, not a church.
Uh, here, in the new Glee Club.
Haven't you heard?
Why wait for Sundays to be
Aretha Franklin and Beyoncé
William McKinley High School?
Miss Jones is listening.
Well, I-I want to audition,
You know, I don't know what song to sing,
I don't know what to do with my hands when I'm singing,
I don't know how to move all cool, like...
I'm this.
But inside, I'm-I'm more.
Okay.
I will help.
First tip:
Which, you know, respect.
But I see the way that you slink around
Mm-hmm.
It's time for your attitude to match your outfits.
I guess I just feel safer
In a way, it lets me feel invisible.
Not anymore.
I think I might know the perfect song for you.
Hello, I'm Kurt Hummel
"Mr. Cellophane."
♪ Cellophane ♪
♪ Mr. Cellophane ♪
♪ Should've been my name ♪
♪ 'Cause you can look right through me ♪
♪ Walk right by me ♪
♪ And never know I'm there ♪
♪ Never ♪
♪ Even ♪
♪ Know... ♪
♪ I'm there. ♪
Thank you. That was... that was really nice.
Hey, Dad!
- I did it.
- Huh?
- I joined a team.
- Hey, hey! All right!
There we go, Kurt!
Which one?
- The Glee Club.
- What's Glee Club?
It's amazing. We-we sing and we dance
Look, uh, Kurt...
I'm all for singing and dancing, but the point of this
Well, Glee Club is-is kind of like that.
At the end of the term, we-we perform
Against other schools, you know?
So it really is like a sports team?
Yeah, yeah, uh, kind of.
Except with choreography and Beyoncé.
Who's Beyoncé? She one of the girls on the team?
No, Dad, she's, like, the biggest pop star in the world.
Oh.
I mean, we-we could use
Okay, good.
This is good.
I still think it'd do you good
Honestly, Dad, I don't think I've ever been this
Thanks for pushing me to do this.
Thanks for showing up for yourself.
Hey, Burt!
Yeah?
What?
I'm gay, Dad.
Please don't stop loving me, but I'm gay.
We good?
I got to go deal with this.
Yeah... yeah, yeah, we're good.
Okay.
Who needs me?
My name is Mercedes Jones,
I mean, it's not like
I get picked on,
I mean, there is that one black kid,
- Hey, Mercedes.
- Yeah. Hi.
I'm a big star at my church,
I got a big-ass voice,
But that's all gonna change real soon
Excuse me, Mercedes Jones?
Hi, I'm Rachel Berry.
I saw that you signed up for the Glee Club. Me, too.
I can tell by your sloppy signature
Which is good, because
I'm very talented, too.
Well, it's nice to meet you, Rachel.
Guess I'll be seeing you in Glee Club.
My dads always say: the person who's better than you,
Okay, let me just stop you right there, because I can see
You're trying to get all
But let me tell you something.
I've been dealing with this kind of nonsense
You go to one of those singing black churches.
That's amazing.
One of my dads is black.
See? Another thing that we have in common.
What?
A black dad.
Okay, girl, I got to go to gym class.
I'd really love to hear you sing one time.
Maybe I could come to your church.
Are you serious?
You want to come to my church?
♪ I may not be the best at anything ♪
♪ Or have the best of anything ♪
♪ Sometimes I feel like ♪
♪ I'm the least of all ♪
♪ But I know someone who has everything ♪
♪ And he's my everything ♪
♪ And I'm happy just to know ♪
♪ That I'm his child ♪
♪ His name is Jesus ♪
♪ The righteous son of God ♪
♪ Lily of the valley ♪
♪ Bright and morning star ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ His name is Jesus ♪
♪ Jesus ♪
♪ He's my everything ♪
♪ I am happy just to know that I'm his child ♪
♪ I may not be the best at anything ♪
♪ Or have the best of anything ♪
♪ Sometimes I feel like ♪
♪ I'm the least of all ♪
♪ But I know someone who has everything ♪
♪ And he's my everything ♪
♪ And I'm happy just to know I'm his child ♪
♪ His name is Jesus ♪
♪ Oh, his name is Jesus ♪
♪ Righteous son of God ♪
♪ He's the righteous son of God ♪
♪ Lily of the valley ♪
♪ Bright and morning star ♪
♪ His name is Jesus ♪
♪ Jesus ♪
♪ He's my everything ♪
♪ I am happy just to know ♪
♪ Happy just to know ♪
♪ That I'm his child. ♪
- Yes, sweetie. Okay, take care of your voice, now. - Okay.
- Okay, bye-bye.
- Mercedes.
I had no idea.
I saw something so special today
Well, I'm pretty sure that you invited you,
I saw Mercedes Jones, future R&B star.
Your audience is gonna love you.
Oh, so I hear what you're saying:
I should've known.
Should've known what?
Rachel Berry, you are officially on notice.
Wherever you think your voice can go, mine will be there, too.
My name is Tina Cohen-Chang,
I'm wildly unpopular, but I love being unpopular.
I'm trying to be unpopular, because I am goth.
Goths have no time for cliché bougie high school cliques.
We are the anti-clique.
What's up,
Wu-Tang witch?
You ride a broomstick or a chop-a-stick?
Eat m-m...
D-Don't stutter.
It's not n-nice.
The joke's on you,
Puckerman... my stutter is fake.
Not even Meryl Streep herself
I could be a big, big star if I weren't so shy.
I need to work on that.
And I also need to
Oh, shut up, Tina, everybody talks to themselves.
Begone, jocks.
Begone, cheerleaders.
You have no power here.
True power comes from nonconformity.
That's why I embrace the avant-garde
What's shakin', bacon?
N-N-Nothing.
My name is Artie Abrams,
She's not only sexy as hell,
Almost everyone else around here looks at me
Tina doesn't look at the chair.
She looks at me.
She jokes with me,
It's nice, because that never happens to me.
She's my best friend.
I love you.
W-W-What?
Nothing.
Uh, let's go eat, woman.
I can't believe you guys did it.
Of course we did it, Autobot,
Yeah, and besides,
Mr. Clarkson, his werewolf heritage is not a real ethnicity
Well, she shouldn't have ditched her otherkin identity.
Quid pro quo, Tina Marie.
W-What does that even m-mean?
Well, Th-that means that it's your turn to accept a dare,
But I think the most fun of all would be
I dare you and Wheels
Fine. Whatever.
Who even cares?
I sure d-don't.
♪ This was never the way I planned ♪
♪ Not my intention ♪
♪ I got so brave, drink in hand ♪
♪ Lost my discretion ♪
♪ It's not what I'm used to ♪
♪ Just wanna try you on ♪
♪ I'm curious for you ♪
♪ Caught my attention ♪
♪ I kissed a girl and I liked it ♪
♪ The taste of her cherry ChapStick ♪
♪ I kissed a girl just to try it ♪
♪ I hope my boyfriend don't mind it ♪
♪ It felt so wrong, it felt so right ♪
♪ Don't mean
I'm in love tonight ♪
♪ I kissed a girl ♪
♪ Just to try it ♪
♪ I liked it. ♪
Wow.
Th-Thanks.
See if you can top that, Wheels.
Damn, girl, you nailed it.
- Uh, you are?
- I'm Artie Abrams,
"Pony" by Ginuwine.
♪ I'm just a bachelor ♪
♪ I'm looking for a partner ♪
♪ Someone who knows how to ride ♪
♪ Without even falling off ♪
♪ Gotta be compatible ♪
♪ Takes me to my limits ♪
♪ Ooh, girl, when I break you off ♪
♪ I promise that you won't want to get off ♪
♪ If you want it ♪
♪ Let's do it ♪
♪ Ride it, my pony ♪
♪ My saddle's waiting ♪
♪ Come and jump on it ♪
♪ If you want it ♪
♪ Let's do it ♪
♪ Ride it, my pony ♪
♪ My saddle's waiting ♪
♪ Come and jump on it ♪
♪ Yeah. ♪
All right, Artie!
That was... that was fun.
Thank you.
- Ginuwine is a badass.
- Artie, that was
I had no idea.
- Really?
- Seriously.
That's the best voice
I have ever heard.
Brad.
Welcome, everybody!
Can I just say what an awesome job
I was... I was blown away.
Okay, so...
"S-S-S..." "Sit Down,
You're Rockin' the Boat"
We did this at
McKinley's Christmas concert
Artie, why don't you take the lead.
- Yes!
- Mr. Schuester.
With all due respect,
I'm the only member here who was
Say what?
It's the first song; it sets the precedent for everything.
Rachel, Artie's gonna sing the first solo, period.
You and everyone else are gonna have plenty
In fact, I was thinking for sectionals, we would do
Who wants the Sandy part?
Is this even a discussion right now?!
I'm the only person in this room who can play Sandy!
- Why? Because you're white?
- Okay, I wouldn't dream
It has to be about who has the best voice.
Exactly. That would be me.
Let's warm up.
Brad.
I thought you were finishing up out here?
I-I was just taking a little break.
You just left the vacuum cleaner on
There is a division of labor in this house, Will.
You do the cooking and cleaning,
Which might not be anytime soon
You're right.
I am stressed.
And I'm sure my sperm's stressed, too.
Mm-hmm.
The Glee Club is one day old, and there's already in-fighting.
Which is kind of my fault,
Just give it to whichever one is the most pathetic.
It's much harder to be jealous of someone when you think
Even if they get something that you want.
I love it when you're all smart.
Oh.
I'm only gonna ask you this once,
Okay.
Is it worth it?
I mean, you know
I'm a little bit psychic.
I have a bad feeling about this.
How could anything bad come out of a glee club?
Because look how distracted you are by it already.
What if you end up spending so much time with the glee kids
I don't want to become one of those ignored wives
You are the love of my life.
And nothing is ever gonna take you away from me.
Good.
Mr. Schuester, how's the search for our male lead going?
I took the initiative of making a list of potential candidates
- based on their yearbook photos.
- Um, thanks, Rachel.
But I was actually headed to the locker room
- to see if, uh, any of the football players signed up. - Great.
I also made a list of all the reasons
I think it would make an important statement
Oh, my God.
A-Are you okay?
I told you.
Everyone hates me.
Everybody up!
We're moving to the auditorium.
Alcoholics Anonymous has the auditorium.
Not anymore.
Principal Figgins believes in us so much,
For a while.
Let's go. And grab a copy of
"You're the One That I Want."
Hold up, who gets to sing the Sandy part?
Rachel.
Are you serious?
I can blow the roof off that auditorium.
Her little bitty Jewish voice won't make it
- past the third row.
- Racist!
And untrue. I can belt just as good as you, better even.
Oh, really?
Well, let's prove it.
Let's have a sing-off right here, right now.
We're not having a sing-off!
Although that's not a bad idea for a future exercise.
Rachel has this solo.
Like I said, you'll all take turns.
Except the white girl goes first.
The white girl always goes first.
Hey.
I didn't get the solo.
I lost it to that demented little Beanie Baby.
Mr. Schuester is never gonna give me a solo.
It's a waste of time;
I'm gonna quit.
Nobody in there is gonna see me the way that I see myself.
Mercedes.
You are so young.
Glee Club just started.
Who knows what your future holds?
Mercedes,
But part of the responsibility
Maybe she's gonna get the solos
Truth is, Mercedes, Rachel will make you better.
Her drive and ambition
And I have a feeling
Stars have a way of finding each other.
Okay, come here.
There you go, Sue.
Some principals would say
The Cheerios! Are McKinley
High's number one priority.
Oh, thank you so much,
Principal Figgins.
I could have never led my Cheerios!
To a record five consecutive national championships
Actually, I could have done it very easily without you.
Oh, uh, and that reminds me.
I have a question for you.
Hmm?
What exactly is going on with Will Schuester
The Glee Club?
Why, Sue, that's nothing but a trifling.
Well, I just want to be clear that the star performers
Oh, Sue, don't worry.
You are my star.
You are on Fox Sports Net.
- Yes. - And besides, show choir won't last.
Will only has five students, one of them a cripple.
And children these days aren't interested
They're too busy with their Friendster and Myspace
These are things that are here to stay.
Well, I don't know.
I have a bad feeling about this Glee Club.
Come on, go!
Okay, come on.
Traveling.
Hey!
Hey, you know, because we're best friends,
I want to ask you something frankly.
Sure.
Wait, I-I'm your best friend?
I-I know nothing about you.
We hardly even talk.
We just play basketball once a week.
Yeah, like I said, best friends.
What are your...
Thank you.
What are your intentions with this Glee Club?
Intentions?
I don't know.
I guess we'll have to find out.
I don't know, I just...
I look around this school,
I see all these kids
A place where they can go to experience the joy of music.
Yeah, well, they already have that, William.
It's called the iPod.
I don't know, being a part
Now you're a high school
Spanish teacher.
Will, the students at this school
They're not gonna become professional singers
They'll be fry cooks and auto mechanics.
And it's really unfair of you to suggest anything otherwise.
Fostering unrealistic dreams in these kids will accomplish
I'm sorry, Sue.
I just disagree.
I mean, the arts are important.
Certainly more important than cheerleading.
How dare you.
And I think, with a little hard work,
I got Finn Hudson to sign up,
I'm gonna give you an ultimatum, William.
You either drop this Glee Club,
What?
Are you serious?
You do not want to make
You don't want to do that.
Sorry, Sue.
No deal.
♪ ♪
The sun is not the biggest nor the brightest star in the sky.
It's just the closest.
There are bigger, brighter, better stars.
That's what I am.
I will be the biggest star of them all.
Myspace is pretty much the greatest invention ever.
It democratizes performance and lets anyone express themself
That's why I invested all of my Bat Mitzvah money
Unfortunately, the Internet
Now people can anonymously say things to me
I am proud to say that I have grown numb
Rumor has it that Mr. Shue's
Time's are tough, and he's probably gonna leave us
That's the inciting incident.
Glee Club is the cosmic explosion that will
Specifically Midtown...
And without Will Schuester,
There's no convincing him to change.
If I want him to give up on this stupid accounting thing,
I have to go talk directly to his boss.
I am very aware that it is the job off the assistant manager
Howard, but I am pregnant,
- Are you on bed rest?
- Oh, not officially,
And even sooner, if you keep stressing me out
No, no, no, I-I'm sorry.
I'll-I'll just give up sleeping for a while to get it all done.
Mrs. Schuester,
I'm Rachel Berry.
I'm one of your husband's students,
Glee Club specifically.
- I'm working.
- First of all,
I just wanted to congratulate you on your new addition.
I can tell that you already have the pregnancy glow.
Oh. Thank you.
Second of all, I just wanted to ask you to reconsider guilting
Here's what I've learned in the years since I left high school.
There's who you are, and there's who you think you are.
And your level of personal misery is determined
It's my job as a wife to help my husband see who he really is,
That's how I keep him happy.
But isn't the point of life to imagine yourself doing something
Yes, if it's realistic.
See, I want a bigger house, and I want to decorate it
But not if I'm gonna let Will ruin it by chasing after a dream
Oh, but he would be helping...
Mainly me...
To achieve my full potential.
That's not gonna help
Mama buy personalized.
Mr. and Mrs. throw pillows from the monogram shop.
Do not put the plush blankets with the novelty sheets!
You're stressing out my baby.
Mrs. Schuester,
I am begging you to reconsider.
Mr. Schuester listens to you.
Yes, because he's my husband.
And it is my job to bring structure to our family,
I always wanted to be in an all-male a Capella group.
I guess my dream is dead, too.
First the almighty Finn
Hudson joins Glee Club,
Then he quits, then he rejoins,
We need him though, Kurt.
Why? Because he's popular?
No, he's not only popular.
He's at the top of the damn
McKinley High food chain.
But I don't know...
Maybe he needs us, too.
Oh, yeah, sure. The guy with the perfect life
Who you calling "damaged goods"?
No one!
I'm just saying that
I don't trust him.
I mean, he already gets everything that he wants.
What is he doing barging into our club and taking it over?
Mark my words, he's gonna get
Cheerios! To join him,
Oh, no.
Nobody pushes out
Mercedes Jones.
Or Kurt Hummel.
I will not allow it.
No, sir.
You know, now that
I think about it,
I cannot believe he convinced me to make our costumes.
Oh, by the way, if you need help with that,
I'm more than happy to pitch in.
You can't go wrong with red and denim.
How did you become so smart and adorable?
Oh.
Baby, can you hand me some sugar?
Sure.
Thanks!
You're the only openly gay person I know.
That is so brave of you.
Well, coming out was
I've ever had to do.
But I'm telling you it feels so nice
So what about you, Joby?
Are you thinking about coming out anytime soon?
What? I-I'm not gay.
I'm straight as an arrow.
I'm attracted to women.
Obviously, of course.
Um, I-I had no idea, I...
I mean, it's obvious that Rachel's only
So do you. No, I don't.
Oh, get real, you do, too.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
Maybe having Finn Hudson around is a mistake.
I'm gonna call an emergency meeting.
And another thing... he wants us to do "Don't Stop Believin'."
Our audience is gonna think we're doing
- You guys started without me?
- Uh, hell yeah, Berry.
- You're, like, ten minutes late.
- You're lucky that I came
That's what this is about.
Okay, we're having second thoughts about him.
For the record, not all of us are.
Okay, we can't kick him out.
I just personally persuaded him to come back.
Them personally persuade him to quit.
It shouldn't be that difficult.
He's already quit once before.
Look, it's obvious that Artie
And honestly I don't care, but he shouldn't be an evil jock.
I don't think that Finn Hudson is evil.
Now, his girlfriend,
Quinn Fabray?
She's a grade-A bitch.
Hey, all I know
Finn Hudson rescued me.
Then, after rehearsal, he wheeled me home.
He wheeled me all the way home,
So, he's not evil.
Not by a long shot.
He's never called me fat.
I mean, that's better than most of the jerks at this school.
I guess when I got tossed into the Dumpster,
That was kind of nice.
He is awfully c-cute.
Maybe he's not that different than us.
Maybe he just
And if we start excluding people,
So far, my time at McKinley has sucked.
But... not this week.
I made some friends.
And that's always been really hard for me.
I don't know what's gonna happen with this club,
Maybe it'll be
When we look back on our time here,
For what we did and-and who we included.
All in favor of keeping Finn in the Glee Club?
Aye.
For the last time, my hands are tied.
I can't offer Will Schuester a raise to run a club
Fine, then we're gonna lose Will
Schuester, and it's gonna be
And that's a fact that wounds me deeply,
Counselor Emma Pillsbury.
I can't offer Will
Schuester more money,
A precious adolescent memory.
I scoured McKinley's archives
Championship
William Schuester.
♪ Burn, baby, burn, disco inferno ♪
♪ Burn that disco down ♪
♪ Burn it down ♪
♪ Burn, baby, burn ♪
♪ We're gonna burn it ♪
♪ Burn it. ♪
Congratulations, buddy.
I just heard the great news.
Oh, thanks. Yeah.
Terri and I are really excited.
We've been talking about kids for a while.
No, not that news. Knocking somebody up isn't difficult
No, I'm talking about your other news,
Oh, uh... You know, to be honest with you,
Nope, accounting is the career for you. Oh, hey,
- I got you a going away present.
- An abacus.
Yeah, the Orientals say it's easier than a calculator,
Oh, and here's five years worth of receipts
You'll be happy to know that your first ever client
And there's an awful lot of bikini waxes in there
♪ Just a small-town girl ♪
♪ Living in a lonely world ♪
♪ She took the midnight train ♪
♪ Going anywhere ♪
♪ Just a city boy ♪
♪ Born and raised in South Detroit ♪
♪ He took the midnight train ♪
♪ Going anywhere ♪
♪ Da, dum ♪
♪ A singer in a smoky room ♪
♪ A smell of wine and cheap perfume ♪
♪ For a smile, they can share the night ♪
♪ It goes on ♪
♪ And on and on and on ♪
♪ Strangers waiting ♪
♪ Da, dum ♪
♪ Up and down the boulevard ♪
♪ Their shadows searching ♪
♪ In the night ♪
♪ Da, dum ♪
♪ Streetlight people ♪
♪ Living just to find emotion ♪
♪ Hiding somewhere ♪
♪ In the night... ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Working hard to get my fill ♪
♪ Everybody wants a thrill ♪
♪ Paying anything to roll the dice ♪
♪ Just one more time ♪
♪ Some will win, some will lose ♪
♪ Some were born to sing the blues ♪
♪ Oh, the movie never ends ♪
♪ It goes on and on ♪
♪ And on and on ♪
♪ Don't stop believin' ♪
♪ Hold on to that feeling ♪
♪ Streetlight people ♪
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ Don't stop believin' ♪
♪ Hold on to that feeling ♪
♪ Streetlight people ♪
♪ Oh... don't stop. ♪
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.MY-SUBS.com